visualwebripper.com 2009-02-15

# Untitled Page

Web Service Share is committed to honoring privacy rights. 

IMPORTANT: BY USING THIS WEB SITE YOU GIVE YOUR CONSENT THAT ALL PERSONAL DATA THAT YOU SUBMIT MAY BE PROCESSED BY Web Service Share FOR THE PURPOSES DESCRIBED IN THE FOLLOWING WEB SITE PRIVACY POLICY.

This privacy policy describes Web Service Share's current policies and practices with regard to personal data collected by Web Service Share through this web site.  The term "personal data" refers to personally identifiable information about you, such as your name, birth date, e-mail address or mailing address.

**Notification of Changes to This Policy**

Web Service Share is continually improving and adding new functionality and features to this web site and improving and adding to its existing products, services and programs.  Because of these ongoing changes, changes in the law and the changing nature of technology, Web Service Share's data practices will change from time to time.  If and when our data practices change, Web Service Share will post the changes on our web site to notify you of the changes.  We encourage you to check this page frequently.  Please rest assured, however, that it is always our intent to comply with the letter and spirit of the Privacy Act.

**Information Gathering and Dissemination Practices**

Our site's registration forms require users and prospective users (together called "users") to give us personal data.  Periodically, we use the information you have provided on the registration form to send you updates about our products and promotional material provided to us by our partners.

The user information is also used to contact the user periodically about the products and services for which the user has signed up, as well as general information about Web Service Share.  In these mailings, we may include offers from our partners, information about product upgrades and enhancements, as well as marketing promotions from Web Service Share.

Anonymous Data Collected Through This Web Site

In addition to the information you provide when you use our web site, Web Service Share may use technology to collect anonymous information about the use of our web site.  For example, we may use technology to track which pages of our web site our visitors view.  We also may use technology to determine which web browsers our visitors use.  This technology does not identify you personally, it simply enables us to compile statistics about our visitors and their use of our site.

We use this anonymous data to improve the content and functionality of this web site and our e-mail updates, to better understand our users and markets, and to improve Web Service Share products and services.

Cookies

In order to collect the anonymous data described in the preceding paragraph, Web Service Share may use temporary "cookies" that collect the first level domain name of the user (for example, if your e-mail address is "jsmith@email.com," the cookie collects the "email.com" portion of your e-mail address) and the date and time you accessed this web site.  Cookies by themselves cannot be used to discover the identity of the user.  A cookie is a small piece of information that is sent to your browser and stored on your computer's hard drive.  Cookies do not damage your computer.  You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie.  This enables you to decide if you want to accept it or not.

Disclosure of Your Personal Data

Web Service Share does not share the personal data we collect when you use this web site with unrelated third parties, except under these limited circumstances:  Personal data may occasionally be transferred to third parties who act for or on behalf of Web Service Share, or in connection with the business of Web Service Share, for further processing in accordance with the purposes for which the data was originally collected or for purposes to which you have subsequently consented.  In addition, there may be some other, limited circumstances in which Web Service Share may share or transfer the information in its databases, for example, to comply with a legal requirement, for the administration of justice, to protect your vital interests, to protect the security or integrity of our databases or this web site, to take precautions against legal liability, or in the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganisation, dissolution or similar event.

**Data Integrity and Security**

Web Service Share strives to maintain the reliability, accuracy, completeness and currency of personal data in our databases and to protect the privacy and security of our databases.  We keep your data only for as long as reasonably necessary for the purposes for which it was collected or to comply with any applicable legal or ethical reporting or document retention requirements.  Our servers and our databases are protected by industry standard security technology, such as industry standard firewalls and password protection.

**Link to Other Sites**

This Privacy Policy applies only to this web site.  This web site may contain hyperlinks to web sites that are not operated by Web Service Share or one of its affiliates.  These hyperlinks are provided for your reference and convenience only and do not imply any endorsement of the activities of these third-party web sites or any association with their operators.  Web Service Share does not control these web sites and is not responsible for their data practices.  We urge you to review the privacy policy posted on any site you visit before using the site or providing any personal data about yourself.

Of course, the Internet is made up of a large number of international connections. If you are visiting this web site from a country other than the country in which our server is located (currently in Australia), the various communications will necessarily result in the transfer of information across international boundaries. By visiting this web site and communicating electronically with us, you consent to these transfers.

**Cancelling Your User Login**

By registering a user account on Web Service Share, you agree that we may contact you regarding your account as described above. To not receive these communications, you may login in and cancel at [ http://www.webserviceshare.com](http://www.webserviceshare.com/).

**Data Access and Corrections.**

This site gives users the ability to change and modify personal information previously provided. Please log into your account at [ http://www.webserviceshare.com](http://www.webserviceshare.com/) to update your user information.

**Governing Law**

This privacy policy forms part of our web site Terms and Conditions and as such shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the Privacy Act. 

**Contacting  Web Service Share About Privacy**

Questions regarding our privacy policy should be directed to the Web Service Share site coordinator, at [privacy@webserviceshare.com](mailto:privacy@webserviceshare.com).  You may also use this address to notify us that you do not wish to receive future mailings from Web Service Share. 

**Effective Date**

The terms and conditions set forth above are effective as of August 1, 2008.
